Guide to the Liederkranz Collection ca. 1847-1987 MSS.130
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Printed Sheet Music Collection, 63573
  - Composer: Sutton, Harry O. Title: In a Kiss Uniform Title: In a Kiss Publisher information: New York: Jos. W. Stern and Co. Plate Number: 4631-3, undated; 31142040612874; 64151 (Box 102, Folder 1363)
  - Composer: Svendsen, Johan S. Title: Abendlied Uniform Title: Abendlied, undated; 31142040613385; 64150 (Box 158, Folder 2507)
  - Composer: Svendsen, Johan Severin, arr. Title: Traume. Studie zu Tristan und Isolde von Richard Wagner Uniform Title: Traume. Studie zu Tristan und Isolde von Richard Wagner Publisher information: Mainz (Germany): B. Schott's Söhne (BB. Schott's Söhne [printer]) Plate Number: 25758, undated; 31142040612809; 64149 (Box 95, Folder 1181)
  - Composer: Svendsen, Johan Severin Title: Kronungs-Marsch Uniform Title: Kronungs-Marsch Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): E. W. Fritzsch (J. Pickenhahn [printer]) Plate Number: E.W.F. 241 L., undated; 31142040612528; 64148 (Box 67, Folder 869)
  - Composer: Svendsen, Johan Severin Title: Kronungs-Marsch Uniform Title: Kronungs-Marsch Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): E. W. Fritzsch Plate Number: E. W. F. 240.L., undated; 31142040612528; 64147 (Box 67, Folder 868)
  - Composer: Svendsen, Johan Severin Title: Rapsodie Norvegienne. No. 3 Uniform Title: Rapsodie norvegienne. No. 3; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 19171-64, undated; 31142040612528; 64146 (Box 67, Folder 864)
  - Composer: Svendsen, Johan Severin Title: Rapsodie Norvegienne. No. 3 Uniform Title: Rapsodie norvegienne. No. 3 Engraver: 12591, undated; 31142040612528; 64145 (Box 67, Folder 862)
  - Composer: Svendsen, Johan Severin Title: Rapsodie Norvegienne. No. 3 Uniform Title: Rapsodie norvegienne. No. 3 Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Carl Warmuths Musikalienverlag Plate Number: C. W. 293, undated; 31142040612528; 64144 (Box 67, Folder 863)
  - Composer: Svendsen, Johan Severin Title: Romance Uniform Title: Romances, violin, orchestra, op. 26 Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 11640, undated; 31142040612528; 64143 (Box 67, Folder 867)
  - Composer: Svendsen, Johan Severin Title: Romanze, op. 26 Uniform Title: Romances, violin, orchestra, op. 26; arr. Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Carl Warmuths Musikalienverlag Plate Number: C. W. 2193 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040612528; 64142 (Box 67, Folder 866)
  - Composer: Svendsen, Johan Severin Title: Romanze, op. 26 Uniform Title: Romances, violin, orchestra, op. 26 Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Carl Warmuths Musikalienverlag Plate Number: C. W. 758 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040612528; 64141 (Box 67, Folder 865)
  - Composer: Taubert, Wilhelm Title: Der Landsknecht Uniform Title: Landsknecht Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Ries and Erler (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 953 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613328; 64140 (Box 164, Folder 2772)
  - Composer: Taubert, Wilhelm Title: Der Landsknecht Uniform Title: Landsknecht Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Ries and Erler (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 965 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613328; 64139 (Box 164, Folder 2773)
  - Composer: Taubert, Wilhelm Title: Der Sturm. Act I Uniform Title: Sturm. Act I Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: 10532, undated; 31142040612510; 64138 (Box 66, Folder 854)
  - Composer: Taubert, Wilhelm Title: Der Sturm. Ouverture Uniform Title: Sturm. Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: 10545, undated; 31142040612510; 64137 (Box 66, Folder 853)
  - Composer: Taubert, Wilhelm Title: Liebesliedchen aus Der Sturm Uniform Title: Sturm. Liebesliedchen Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: Part.B.1301., undated; 31142040612833; 64136 (Box 98, Folder 1244)
  - Composer: Taubert, Wilhelm Title: Liebesliedchen Uniform Title: Liebesliedchen Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: K.M.663., undated; 31142040612833; 64135 (Box 98, Folder 1245)
  - Composer: Tausche, Emil Title: Am sonnigen Rhein Uniform Title: Am sonnigen Rhein Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. W. Siegel's Musikalienhandlung (E. Jul. Pickenhahn [printer]) Plate Number: 7925, undated; 31142040613427; 64134 (Box 154, Folder 2345)
  - Composer: Tavan-Marchetti Title: La Fete de Seville Uniform Title: La Fete de Seville; arr. Publisher information: New York: Ross Jungnickel Plate Number: 36-98, undated; 31142040614185; 64133 (Box 38, Folder 452)
  - Composer: Techritz, Johannes Title: Ade denn, du stolze Uniform Title: Ade denn, du stolze Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Gebruder Hug and Co. (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: G.H.1796 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613435; 64132 (Box 153, Folder 2307)
  - Composer: Techritz, Johannes Title: Volkslieder aus dem XVI. Jahrhundert Uniform Title: Volkslieder aus dem XVI. Jahrhundert, undated; 31142040613401; 64131 (Box 156, Folder 2448)
  - Composer: Thelen, A. Title: Abend am Rhein Uniform Title: Abend am Rhein Publisher information: Offenbach a/M (Germany): Johann Andre Plate Number: ANDRE 16521, undated; 31142040613492; 64130 (Box 147, Folder 2104)
  - Composer: Thern, Carl Title: Genius Loci Uniform Title: Genius loci Publisher information: Weimar (Germany): T. F. A. Kuhn (F. W. Garbrecht, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: K.315 W. Engraver: F. W. Garbrecht, Leipzig, undated; 31142040612833; 64129 (Box 98, Folder 1250)
  - Composer: Thieriot, Ferdinand Title: Am Traunsee Uniform Title: Traunsee Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): E. W. Fritzsch (J. Pickenhahn, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: E.W.F. 64 L. Engraver: Friedrich Kratschmer, undated; 31142040612858; 64128 (Box 100, Folder 1302)
  - Composer: Thomas, A. Goring (Arthur Goring) Title: The Sun-Worshippers. A Choral Ode Uniform Title: Sun-Worshippers Publisher information: London (Great Britain): Novello, Ewer and Co. Plate Number: 6165, undated; 31142040612668; 64127 (Box 81, Folder 1036)
  - Composer: Thomas, Ambroise Title: Entr'Acte. Gavotte Uniform Title: Mignon. Entr'Acte; Gavotte; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 3873-47, undated; 31142040612536; 64126 (Box 68, Folder 876)
  - Composer: Thomas, Ambroise Title: Entr'Acte. Gavotte Uniform Title: Mignon. Entr'Acte; Gavotte; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 5958, undated; 31142040612536; 64125 (Box 68, Folder 877)
  - Composer: Thomas, Ambroise Title: Le Caid. Overture Uniform Title: Caid. Ouverture; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 5579-31, undated; 31142040612536; 64124 (Box 68, Folder 878)
  - Composer: Thomas, Ambroise Title: Mignon. Ouverture; Entr'acte Uniform Title: Mignon. Ouverture; Entr'acte Publisher information: Paris (France): Heugel et Cie. Plate Number: H. 4682, undated; 31142040612536; 64123 (Box 68, Folder 874)
  - Composer: Thomas, Ambroise Title: Mignon. Overture Uniform Title: Mignon. Ouverture; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 22295-80, undated; 31142040612536; 64122 (Box 68, Folder 875)
  - Composer: Thomas, Ambroise Title: Ouverture zur Oper Der Kadi Uniform Title: Caid. Ouverture; arr. Publisher information: Mainz (Germany): B. Schott's Söhne Plate Number: 25974, undated; 31142040612536; 64121 (Box 68, Folder 879)
  - Composer: Thomas, Ambroise Title: Raymond Overture Uniform Title: Raymond, ou le Scret de la Reine. Ouverture; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 12841-53, undated; 31142040612536; 64120 (Box 68, Folder 882)
  - Composer: Thomas, Ambroise Title: Raymond Overture Uniform Title: Raymond, ou le Scret de la Reine. Ouverture; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 2361-44, undated; 31142040612536; 64119 (Box 68, Folder 883)
  - Composer: Thomas, Ambroise Title: Raymond Overture Uniform Title: Raymond, ou le Scret de la Reine. Ouverture Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 7971-10, undated; 31142040612536; 64118 (Box 68, Folder 881)
  - Composer: Thomas, Ambroise Title: Raymond, ou le Secret de la Reine. Overture Uniform Title: Raymond, ou le Scret de la Reine. Ouverture Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 25525, undated; 31142040612536; 64117 (Box 68, Folder 880)
  - Composer: Thomas, Arthur Goring Title: The Sun-Worshippers Uniform Title: Adorateurs du Soleil Publisher information: London (Great Britain): Novello, Ewer and Co. Plate Number: 6165, undated; 31142040613500; 64116 (Box 146, Folder 2066)
  - Composer: Thomas, Arthur Goring Title: The Sun-Worshippers Uniform Title: Adorateurs du Soleil Publisher information: London (Great Britain): Novello, Ewer and Co. Plate Number: 6187, undated; 31142040613500; 64115 (Box 146, Folder 2067)
  - Composer: Thomas, Carl Title: Elka-March Uniform Title: Elka-March Publisher information: New York, undated; 31142040612536; 64114 (Box 68, Folder 884)
  - Composer: Thome, Francis Title: Badinage Uniform Title: Badinage Publisher information: Paris (France): Henri Heugel (Fouquet [printer]) Plate Number: H. 7915 Engraver: J. Guillemard, undated; 31142040612510; 64113 (Box 66, Folder 856)
  - Composer: Thome, Francis Title: Badinage Uniform Title: Badinage Publisher information: Paris (France): Henri Heugel Plate Number: H. 7914, undated; 31142040612510; 64112 (Box 66, Folder 855)
  - Composer: Thome, Francis Title: Crepuscule (Twilight) Uniform Title: Crepuscule Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 14838, undated; 31142040612908; 64111 (Box 105, Folder 1477)
  - Composer: Thome, Francis Title: Entracte-Pizzicato Uniform Title: Entracte-Pizzicato Publisher information: Paris (France): Henri Lemoine Plate Number: 8483. HL., undated; 31142040612510; 64110 (Box 66, Folder 857)
  - Composer: Thome, Francis Title: Entracte-Pizzicato Uniform Title: Entracte-Pizzicato Publisher information: Paris (France): Henry Lemoine Plate Number: 8484. HL., undated; 31142040612510; 64109 (Box 66, Folder 858)
  - Composer: Thome, Francis Title: Simple Aveu (Simple Confession) Uniform Title: Simple Aveu Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 4397, undated; 31142040612874; 64108 (Box 102, Folder 1328)
  - Composer: Thome, Francis Title: Simple aveu Uniform Title: Simple aveu Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 3402-7, undated; 31142040612890; 64107 (Box 104, Folder 1398)
  - Composer: Thompson, John, arr. Title: World Famous Melodies. 48 Easy-to-Play Piano Arrangements Uniform Title: World Famous Melodies Publisher information: Cincinnati: The Willis Music Co. Plate Number: W. M. Co. 7336, undated; 31142040613369; 64106 (Box 160, Folder 2587)
  - Composer: Thompson, Kay, arr. Title: Vive l'amour Uniform Title: Vive l'amour; arr., undated; 31142040613443; 64105 (Box 152, Folder 2292)
  - Composer: Thompson, William L. Title: Come Where the Lilies Bloom Uniform Title: Come Where the Lilies Bloom; arr. Publisher information: Boston: Oliver Ditson Company Plate Number: 5-115-70470-10, undated; 31142040613450; 64104 (Box 151, Folder 2210)
  - Composer: Thuille, Ludwig Title: Husarenglaube Uniform Title: Husarenglaube Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Gebruder Hug and Co. (F. M. Geidel, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: G. H. 3946, undated; 31142040613344; 64103 (Box 162, Folder 2662)
  - Composer: Thuille, Ludwig Title: Jugend Uniform Title: Jugend Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Gebruder Hug and Co. Plate Number: G.H.2894, undated; 31142040613328; 64102 (Box 164, Folder 2754)
  - Composer: Thuille, Ludwig Title: Rosenlied Uniform Title: Rosenlied Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 5608 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613278; 64101 (Box 169, Folder 2972)
  - Composer: Tinel, Edgar Title: Sonnengesang aus dem Oratorium Franziskus Uniform Title: Franciscus. Sonnengesang Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: 18749, undated; 31142040613005; 64100 (Box 115, Folder 1635)
  - Composer: Tinel, Edgar Title: Sonnengesang aus dem Oratorium Franziskus Uniform Title: Franciscus. Sonnengesang Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: Ch.B.452., undated; 31142040613500; 64099 (Box 146, Folder 2059)
  - Composer: Tinel, Edgar Title: Sonnengesang aus dem Oratorium Franziskus Uniform Title: Franciscus. Sonnengesang Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: Ch.B.452.A., undated; 31142040613005; 64098 (Box 115, Folder 1637)
  - Composer: Tinel, Edgar Title: Sonnengesang aus dem Oratorium Franziskus Uniform Title: Franciscus. Sonnengesang Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: Orch.B.742., undated; 31142040613005; 64097 (Box 115, Folder 1636)
  - Composer: Tobani, Theodore Moses, arr. Title: Album of National Anthems, Hymns and Patriotic Songs Uniform Title: Album of National Anthems, Hymns andamp; Patriotic Songs Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 3622, undated; 31142040612601; 64096 (Box 75, Folder 970)
  - Composer: Tobani, Theodore Moses Title: Around the Christmas Tree. A Yule-Tide Potpourri Uniform Title: Around the Christmas Tree Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 12338-52, undated; 31142040613039; 64095 (Box 118, Folder 1686)
  - Composer: Tobani, Theodore Moses Title: Crème de la Crème. Musical Melange Uniform Title: Crème de la Crème Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 4329-66, undated; 31142040612924; 64094 (Box 107, Folder 1519)
  - Composer: Tobani, Theodore Moses Title: Daisy-Polka Uniform Title: Daisy Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 4087-18, undated; 31142040613088; 64093 (Box 123, Folder 1769)
  - Composer: Tobani, Theodore Moses Title: German Liederkranz No. 1. Fantasia on German Songs Uniform Title: German Liederkranz No. 1 Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 3857-52, undated; 31142040613468; 64092 (Box 150, Folder 2193)
  - Composer: Tobani, Theodore Moses Title: Hearts and Flowers Uniform Title: Hearts and Flowers; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 11355-6, undated; 31142040613419; 64091 (Box 155, Folder 2438)
  - Composer: Tobani, Theodore Moses Title: Hearts and Flowers Uniform Title: Hearts and Flowers Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 3746-4, undated; 31142040612908; 64090 (Box 105, Folder 1448)
  - Composer: Tobani, Theodore Moses Title: Poetica. Waltz Uniform Title: Poetica. Waltz Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 6628-6, undated; 31142040612874; 64089 (Box 102, Folder 1358)
  - Composer: Tobani, Theodore Moses Title: The White Squadron. Two-Step Uniform Title: White Squadron Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 4029-18, undated; 31142040613070; 64088 (Box 122, Folder 1749)
  - Composer: Tottmann, Albert Title: Dornroschen Uniform Title: Dornroschen Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Hofmeister (Carl Schulze, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 6422, undated; 31142040613591; 64087 (Box 137, Folder 1921)
  - Composer: Tottmann, Albert Title: Dornroschen Uniform Title: Dornroschen Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Hofmeister (Carl Schulze, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 6473, undated; 31142040613591; 64086 (Box 137, Folder 1922)
  - Composer: Traditional German Title: O Tannenbaum Uniform Title: O Tannenbaum; arr. Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 43076, undated; 31142040613484; 64085 (Box 148, Folder 2129)
  - Composer: Traditional Sicilian Melody Title: O Sanctissima Uniform Title: O Sanctissima; arr. Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 43075, undated; 31142040613484; 64084 (Box 148, Folder 2128)
  - Composer: Traditional Title: America Uniform Title: America; arr. Plate Number: 29482-22, undated; 31142040613120; 64083 (Box 127, Folder 1853)
  - Composer: Triest, Heinrich Title: Ein Sommertag Uniform Title: Sommertag Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Carl Simon (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: C.S. 560/62, undated; 31142040612536; 64082 (Box 68, Folder 885)
  - Composer: Trotere, Henry Title: In Old Madrid Uniform Title: In Old Madrid Publisher information: New York: William A. Pond and Co. Plate Number: 12319, undated; 31142040612874; 64081 (Box 102, Folder 1364)
  - Composer: Tschaikowsky [Tschaikovsky], Peter Illich, arr. Title: Mozartiana. Suite no. 4 Uniform Title: Mozartiana. Suite no. 4; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 22207-130, undated; 31142040612544; 64080 (Box 69, Folder 897)
  - Composer: Tschaikowsky [Tschaikovsky], Peter Illich, arr. Title: Mozartiana. Suite no. 4 Uniform Title: Mozartiana. Suite no. 4 Publisher information: Hamburg (Germany): D. Rahter Plate Number: 13639 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040612544; 64079 (Box 69, Folder 896)
  - Composer: Tschaikowsky [Tschaikovsky], Peter Illich Title: 1812 Ouverture Solenelle Uniform Title: 1812 overture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): D. Rahter Plate Number: 1182, undated; 31142040612551; 64078 (Box 70, Folder 900)
  - Composer: Tschaikowsky [Tschaikovsky], Peter Illich Title: 1812 Overture Uniform Title: 1812 overture; arr. Publisher information: New York: Century Music Publishing Co. Plate Number: 3561-6, undated; 31142040613377; 64077 (Box 159, Folder 2580)
  - Composer: Tschaikowsky [Tschaikovsky], Peter Illich Title: Capriccio Italien Uniform Title: Capriccio Italien Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): D. Rahter (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 452, undated; 31142040612544; 64076 (Box 69, Folder 898)
  - Composer: Tschaikowsky [Tschaikovsky], Peter Illich Title: Capriccio Italien Uniform Title: Capriccio Italien Publisher information: London (Great Britain): Hawkes and Son Plate Number: H. and S. 4322, undated; 31142040612544; 64075 (Box 69, Folder 899)
  - Composer: Tschaikowsky [Tschaikovsky], Peter Illich Title: Chanson sans Paroles Uniform Title: Song Without Words; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 5938-34, undated; 31142040612551; 64074 (Box 70, Folder 910)
  - Composer: Tschaikowsky [Tschaikovsky], Peter Illich Title: Eugene Oneguine. Selection Uniform Title: Evgenii Onegin. Selection; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 12701-52, undated; 31142040612551; 64073 (Box 70, Folder 907)
  - Composer: Tschaikowsky [Tschaikovsky], Peter Illich Title: Eugene Oneguine. Waltz Uniform Title: Evgenii Onegin. Waltz; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 12709, undated; 31142040612551; 64072 (Box 70, Folder 906)
  - Composer: Tschaikowsky [Tschaikovsky], Peter Illich Title: Humoresque Uniform Title: Humoresque; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 22384-24, undated; 31142040612551; 64071 (Box 70, Folder 902)
  - Composer: Tschaikowsky [Tschaikovsky], Peter Illich Title: La Belle au Bois Dormant. Ballet Uniform Title: Sleeping Beauty. Ballet Publisher information: Moscow (Russia): P. Jurgenson Plate Number: 17155, undated; 31142040612551; 64070 (Box 70, Folder 908)
  - Composer: Tschaikowsky [Tschaikovsky], Peter Illich Title: Marche Slave Uniform Title: Marche Slave; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 14080-120, undated; 31142040612544; 64069 (Box 69, Folder 895)
  - Composer: Tschaikowsky [Tschaikovsky], Peter Illich Title: Meditation Uniform Title: Meditation, op. 42, no. 1; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 21851-46, undated; 31142040612551; 64068 (Box 70, Folder 903)
  - Composer: Tschaikowsky [Tschaikovsky], Peter Illich Title: Pilgrim's Song Uniform Title: Pilgrim's Song; arr. Publisher information: New York, undated; 31142040613385; 64067 (Box 158, Folder 2511)
  - Composer: Tschaikowsky [Tschaikovsky], Peter Illich Title: Sinfonie Nr. 4 f-Moll Uniform Title: Symphony no. 4, F minor, op. 36 Plate Number: O. B. 2934/31615, undated; 31142040612536; 64066 (Box 68, Folder 891)
  - Composer: Tschaikowsky [Tschaikovsky], Peter Illich Title: Suite from the Casse-Noisette Ballet. Part 1 Uniform Title: Nutcracker. Suite; arr. Publisher information: London (Great Britain): Hawkes and Son Plate Number: H. and S. 3331, undated; 31142040612551; 64065 (Box 70, Folder 901)
  - Composer: Tschaikowsky [Tschaikovsky], Peter Illich Title: Suite from the Casse-Noisette Ballet. Part 2 Uniform Title: Nutcracker. Suite Publisher information: London (Great Britain): Hawkes and Son Plate Number: H. and S. 3332, undated; 31142040612544; 64064 (Box 69, Folder 894)
  - Composer: Tschaikowsky [Tschaikovsky], Peter Illich Title: Suite. Der Nussknacker Uniform Title: Nutcracker. Suite Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): D. Rahter Plate Number: 319, undated; 31142040612544; 64063 (Box 69, Folder 893)
  - Composer: Tschaikowsky [Tschaikovsky], Peter Illich Title: Symphonie IV Uniform Title: Symphony no. 4, F minor, op. 36 Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): D. Rahter Plate Number: 366, undated; 31142040612536; 64062 (Box 68, Folder 890)
  - Composer: Tschaikowsky [Tschaikovsky], Peter Illich Title: Symphonie No. 4 Uniform Title: Symphony no. 4, F minor, op. 36 Publisher information: Moscow (Russia): P. Jurgenson Plate Number: 3377, undated; 31142040612536; 64061 (Box 68, Folder 892)
  - Composer: Tschaikowsky [Tschaikovsky], Peter Illich Title: Symphonie Nr. 4, f-moll, op. 36 Uniform Title: Symphony no. 4, F minor, op. 36 Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel, undated; 31142040612536; 64060 (Box 68, Folder 889)
  - Composer: Tschaikowsky [Tschaikovsky], Peter Illich Title: Symphony no. 4, F minor, op. 36 Uniform Title: Symphony no. 4, F minor, op. 36 Publisher information: New York: Edwin F. Kalmus, undated; 31142040612536; 64059 (Box 68, Folder 888)
  - Composer: Tschaikowsky [Tschaikovsky], Peter Illich Title: Valse de l'Opera Eugene Oneguine Uniform Title: Evgenii Onegin. Waltz Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): D. Rahter Plate Number: 1540. 2840. 2882, undated; 31142040612551; 64058 (Box 70, Folder 905)
  - Composer: Tschaikowsky [Tschaikovsky], Peter Illich Title: Waltz from Dornroschen Uniform Title: Sleeping Beauty. Waltz; arr. Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 21981, undated; 31142040612551; 64057 (Box 70, Folder 909)
  - Composer: Tschaikowsky [Tschaikovsky], Peter Illich Title: Walzer aus Eugen Onegin Uniform Title: Evgenii Onegin. Waltzes Publisher information: Hamburg (Germany): D. Rahter (P. Jurgenson, Moscow [printer]) Plate Number: 15774 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040612551; 64056 (Box 70, Folder 904)
  - Composer: Tschaikowsky, Peter Ilich Title: 5.Symphonie Uniform Title: Symphony no. 5, op. 64, E minor Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): D. Rahter (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 2924, undated; 31142040612528; 64055 (Box 67, Folder 870)
  - Composer: Tschaikowsky, Peter Ilich Title: 5me. Symphonie Uniform Title: Symphony no. 5, op. 64, E minor Plate Number: 13992, undated; 31142040612528; 64054 (Box 67, Folder 871)
  - Composer: Tschaikowsky, Peter Ilich Title: Andante cantabile aus dem Streichquartett Op. 11 Uniform Title: String quartet, op. 11, Bb major. Andante cantabile Publisher information: Heilbronn a/N (Germany): C. F. Schmidt (W. Benicke, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: C. F. S. 854.856.860, undated; 31142040612817; 64053 (Box 96, Folder 1192)